Like, the power of our minds and the ability of manifestation, we just, as a collective, haven't come together.
What you focus on expands, right?
And if everything and everywhere is already created in the quantum realm, then we can literally all be on the same synced page and have the clarity of vision of what, like, we want to see.
And it's just that.
I know people, like, if they haven't come on this journey yet, they're like, what the hell is she talking about?
But if we can manifest on the individual level, we can also manifest in the collective level.
And that's what we've been doing, but we've only been manifesting the trauma and the violence and the, you know, the trauma patterns from our past.
That's why I keep calling it trauma patterns, because we haven't known anything else.
And so that's why number three is creativity.
Like, we need to use our imagination and our ability to be so delusional that there is a timeline that is emerging because timelines are working all at the same time.
But we can't see it yet.
We're all focusing our attention on the death of this thing.
We're all focusing on, like, the ice raids and the bombing.
But that is the death.
That's the physical manifestation of a death of empire.
But there's something else emerging that we also have to focus our attention on and start creating the structure, Saturn, the structure to let it emerge.
But that's why it's important for people to grieve.
You have to grieve what was and continue to do that transmuting process.
That's why this is deeply spiritual work, because you can't move forward if you haven't grieved the past.
So for those of us who have done that work for the last two years, it's our responsibility to hold the vision for the future that people don't see yet.
Like, there's the prophetic people that can already see that.
And I feel like I'm one of those people.
Like, I'm already living in a timeline that's, like, not...
She says this all the time.
I say this all the time.
I'm like, Amanda, my consciousness is, like, 10 years from now, and it looks great.
We just have to...
And then I come back to this timeline, and I'm like, okay, people, like, this is what we got to do, you know?
And so we need people.
We need...
Lurical behaviors.
Literally.
Oh, my God.
I love that.
We need those people who are the death doulas of empire.
Like, we need the people who are in this moment, right?
We need those people.
Everybody has a role.
And then we need the people who are ushering in and focusing our attention.
That's why we need to share our ideas.
Yes.
Like, what do you see?
What does it feel like?
This is all a part of, like, manifestation, but we have to collectively do it now.